export default {
  id: 'low_1006_4_1b',
  name: '상용한자(4학년-1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:くわ(わる)、くわ(える)/음:か', answer: ['加'] },
    { question: '독:まち/음:がい、かい', answer: ['街'] },
    { question: '독:おのおの/음:かく', answer: ['各'] },
    { question: '독:おぼ(える)、さ(ます)、さ(める)/음:かく', answer: ['覚'] },
    { question: '독:편안할/음:こう', answer: ['康'] },
    { question: '독:あらた(める)、あらた(まる)/음:かい', answer: ['改'] },
    { question: '독:あ(げる)、あ(がる)/음:きょ', answer: ['挙'] },
    { question: '독:た(てる)、た(つ)/음:けん、こん', answer: ['建'] },
    { question: '독:すこ(やか)/음:けん', answer: ['健'] },
    { question: '독:か(ける)、か(く)/음:けつ', answer: ['欠'] },
    { question: '독:むす(ぶ)、ゆ(う)、ゆ(わえる)/음:けつ', answer: ['結'] },
    { question: '독:볕/음:けい', answer: ['景'] },
    { question: '독:지름길/음:けい', answer: ['径'] },
    { question: '독:きそ(う)、せ(る)/음:きょう、けい', answer: ['競'] },
    { question: '독:かがみ/음:きょう', answer: ['鏡'] },
    { question: '독:계절/음:き', answer: ['季'] },
    { question: '독:기계/음:かい', answer: ['械'] },
    { question: '독:かた(める)、かた(まる)、かた(い)/음:こ', answer: ['固'] },
    { question: '독:つ(げる)/음:こく', answer: ['告'] },
    { question: '독:공/음:こう、く', answer: ['功'] },
    { question: '독:とも/음:きょう', answer: ['共'] },
    { question: '독:は(たす)、は(てる)、は(て)/음:か', answer: ['果'] },
    { question: '독:공부할/음:か', answer: ['課'] },
    { question: '독:벼슬/음:かん', answer: ['官'] },
    { question: '독:くだ/음:かん', answer: ['管'] },
    { question: '독:せき、かか(わる)/음:かん', answer: ['関'] },
    { question: '독:볼/음:かん', answer: ['観'] },
    { question: '독:もと(める)/음:きゅう', answer: ['求'] },
    { question: '독:すく(う)/음:きゅう', answer: ['救'] },
    { question: '독:군사/음:ぐん', answer: ['軍'] },
    { question: '독:고을/음:ぐん', answer: ['郡'] },
    { question: '독:きわ(める)、きわ(まる)、きわ(み)/음:きょく、ごく', answer: ['極'] },
    { question: '독:줄/음:きゅう', answer: ['給'] },
    { question: '독:벼리/음:き', answer: ['紀'] },
    { question: '독:うつわ/음:き', answer: ['器'] },
    { question: '독:はた(베틀)/음:き', answer: ['機'] },
    { question: '독:はた(깃발)/음:き', answer: ['旗'] },
    { question: '독:생각/음:ねん', answer: ['念'] },
    { question: '독:つと(める)/음:ど', answer: ['努'] },
    { question: '독:홑/음:たん', answer: ['単'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:どう', answer: ['堂'] },
    { question: '독:통달할/음:たつ', answer: ['達'] },
    { question: '독:무리/음:たい', answer: ['隊'] },
    { question: '독:お(びる)、おび/음:たい', answer: ['帯'] },
    { question: '독:무리/음:と', answer: ['徒'] },
    { question: '독:독/음:どく', answer: ['毒'] },
    { question: '독:はたら(く)/음:どう', answer: ['働'] },
    { question: '독:え(る)、う(る)/음:とく', answer: ['得'] },
    { question: '독:ひ/음:とう', answer: ['灯'] },
    { question: '독:つめ(たい)、ひ(える)、ひ(や)、ひ(やす)、ひや(かす)、さ(める)、さ(ます)/음:れい', answer: ['冷'] },
    { question: '독:はか(る)/음:りょう', answer: ['量'] },
    { question: '독:よ(い)/음:りょう', answer: ['良'] },
    { question: '독:지낼/음:れき', answer: ['歴'] },
    { question: '독:つ(れ)る、つら(なる)、つら(ねる)/음:れん', answer: ['連'] },
    { question: '독:하여금/음:れい', answer: ['令'] },
    { question: '독:たと(える)/음:れい', answer: ['例'] },
    { question: '독:일할/음:ろう', answer: ['労'] },
    { question: '독:お(いる)、ふ(ける)/음:ろう', answer: ['老'] },
    { question: '독:기록할/음:ろく', answer: ['録'] },
    { question: '독:헤아릴/음:りょう', answer: ['料'] },
    { question: '독:たぐい/음:るい', answer: ['類'] },
    { question: '독:뭍/음:りく', answer: ['陸'] },
    { question: '독:わ/음:りん', answer: ['輪'] },
    { question: '독:き(く)/음:り', answer: ['利'] },
    { question: '독:み(ちる)、み(たす)/음:まん', answer: ['満'] },
    { question: '독:すえ/음:まつ、ばつ', answer: ['末'] },
    { question: '독:のぞ(む)/음:ぼう、もう', answer: ['望'] },
    { question: '독:うめ/음:ばい', answer: ['梅'] },
    { question: '독:줄기/음:みゃく', answer: ['脈'] },
    { question: '독:まき/음:ぼく', answer: ['牧'] },
    { question: '독:な(い)/음:む、ぶ', answer: ['無'] },
    { question: '독:아닐/음:み', answer: ['未'] },
    { question: '독:たみ/음:みん', answer: ['民'] },
    { question: '독:넓을/음:はく、ばく', answer: ['博'] },
    { question: '독:めし/음:はん', answer: ['飯'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:ほう、はっ、ほっ', answer: ['法'] },
    { question: '독:あた(り)、べ/음:へん', answer: ['辺'] },
    { question: '독:か(わる)、か(える)/음:へん', answer: ['変'] },
    { question: '독:わか(れる)/음:べつ', answer: ['別'] },
    { question: '독:군사/음:へい、ひょう', answer: ['兵'] },
    { question: '독:おっと/음:ふ、ふう', answer: ['夫'] },
    { question: '독:つ(く)、つ(ける)/음:ふ', answer: ['付'] },
    { question: '독:마을/음:ふ', answer: ['府'] },
    { question: '독:버금/음:ふく', answer: ['副'] },
    { question: '독:こ、こな/음:ふん', answer: ['粉'] },
    { question: '독:아닐/음:ふ、ぶ', answer: ['不'] },
    { question: '독:と(ぶ)、と(ばす)/음:ひ', answer: ['飛'] },
    { question: '독:つい(やす)、つい(える)/음:ひ', answer: ['費'] },
    { question: '독:선비/음:し', answer: ['士'] },
    { question: '독:사기/음:し', answer: ['史'] },
    { question: '독:맡을/음:し', answer: ['司'] },
    { question: '독:や(める)/음:じ', answer: ['辞'] },
    { question: '독:う(む)、う(まれる)、う(ぶ)/음:さん', answer: ['産'] },
    { question: '독:ち(る)、ち(らす)、ち(らかす)、ち(らかる)/음:さん', answer: ['散'] },
    { question: '독:ころ(す)/음:さつ、さい、せつ', answer: ['殺'] },
    { question: '독:코끼리/음:しょう、ぞう', answer: ['象'] },
    { question: '독:상줄/음:しょう', answer: ['賞'] },
    { question: '독:자리/음:せき', answer: ['席'] },
    { question: '독:えら(ぶ)/음:せん', answer: ['選'] },
    { question: '독:と(く)/음:せつ、ぜい', answer: ['説'] }
  ]
}
